Guide to the Time Inc. Index Cards 1933-1993, undated MS 3009-RG 4
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: Time, 1936-1987; 134 Linear feet (134 boxes)
  - 1983-1987
    - Allis, Sam -- Borysewicz, Edward (Offsite-box 165)
    - Bo's Going to Follow His Dream -- Congress (Offsite-box 166)
    - Congress -- Exchange Rates (Offsite-box 167)
    - Exchange Rates -- Heller, Walter (Offsite-box 168)
    - Heller, Walter -- Labor (Offsite-box 169)
    - Labor -- Motaung, Marcus (Offsite-box 170)
    - Mote, Robert -- Politics (Offsite-box 171)
    - Politics -- Russel, George (Offsite-box 172)
    - Russell, George -- Tanks (Storage)-Mexico (Offsite-box 173)
    - Tanks (Storage)-Mexico -- Viet Nam (Offsite-box 174)
    - Viet Cong -- Zysman, John (Offsite-box 175)
- Series VIII: Time Advertising Promotion, 1923-1971; 1 Linear feet (1 box)
  Materials in this series are arranged in their original alphabetical order.
  Time Advertising Promotion includes index cards which act as a directory for advertising campaigns which took place between 1923 and 1971 in Time magazine. Each index card contains a list of advertisements. Additionally, the cards sometimes include information about the edition the advertisement was in as well as memos, research report numbers, direct mail numbers, and miscellaneous notes.
  - Time Advertising Promotion, 1923-1971 (Offsite-box 242)
- Series IX: Time Canada, 1967; 1 Linear feet (1 box)
  All materials in this series are arranged in their original alphabetical order.
  Time Canada contains index cards that serve as a directory for subject terms. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief description of a topic related to that term, and the date when the topic was covered in the magazine. The topics covered on the index cards include people, places, events, organizations, and objects.
  - Time Canada, 1967 (Offsite-box 122)
- Series X: Time Inc. History Project, undated; 3 Linear feet (3 boxes)
  Time Inc. History Project contains index cards related to the research Alex Groner and Celia Sugarman completed for their project on the history of Times Inc. As part of their research, Groner and Sugarman created four sets of index cards. The Alumni Directory contains the names of those who worked at Time Inc. prior to 1958. Books by Time contains books that were either written by Time Inc staff or published by Time Inc in or prior to 1958. The Interview Names Index contains index cards with the names of those Groner and Sugarman interviewed as part of their project. These cards contain the person's name, the topics they were being interviewed about, and the date they were interviewed. Individual index cards sometimes contain the record of multiple interviews that were conducted with the same person. The Interview Subjects Index contains cards that act as a subject cross-reference to the Interview Names Index. These index cards contain a subject term, the name of the person who was interviewed, and the date the interview took place.
  This series is arranged into 4 subseries: Alumni Directory, Books by Time, Interview Name Index, and Interview Subject Index. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically either by last name or subject as per the original order.
  - Subseries X.A: Alumni Directory, undated (Offsite-box 506)
  - Subseries X.B: Books by Time, undated (Offsite-box 506)
  - Subseries X.C: Interview Names Index (1 of 2), undated (Offsite-box 504)
  - Subseries X.C: Interview Names Index (2 of 2), undated (Offsite-box 505)
  - Subseries X.D: Interview Subjects Index, undated (Offsite-box 505)
- Series XI: Time International, 1973-1989; 8 Linear feet (8 boxes)
  The index cards in this series are kept in their original order of two chronological groups: 1973-1983 and 1983-1989. The original alphabetical arrangement within each group is also maintained.
  Time International contains index cards that serve as a subject cross-reference for Time International publications. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief description of a topic related to that term, and the date when the topic was covered in the magazine.
  - 1973-1983
    - Aaiun Spanish Sahara -- Economy-Spain (Offsite-box 178)
    - Economy-Spain -- Long Night of Martal Law (Offsite-box 179)
    - Longo, Luigi -- Schmidt, Helmut (Offsite-box 180)
    - Schmidt, Helmut -- 72-Hour Document (Offsite-box 181)
  - 1983-1989
    - A&W Root Beer -- Elizabeth, Queen Mother of Great Britain (Offsite-box 182)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain -- Merrithew, Jim (Offsite-box 183)
    - Merrithew, Jim -- Tanks (Offsite-box 184)
    - Tanks -- Zylberztein (Offsite-box 185)
- Series XII: Time-Life International Advertising Promotion Index, approximately 1940-1966; 1 Linear feet (1 box)
  Materials are arranged in their original order of two alphabetical groups.
  Time-Life International Advertising Promotion includes index cards which act as a directory for advertising campaigns. Each index card contains a list of information including summaries of advertising campaigns and the year the campaign took place. Sometimes research report, promotion, and memo numbers were included. Materials are from approximately the mid-1940s through 1966.
  - Time-Life International Advertising Promotion Index, approximately 1940-1966 (Offsite-box 242)
- Series XIII: Unfiled, 1943-1987; 1 Linear feet (1 box)
  Unfiled contains index cards that were found loose. Based on the original arrangement and separation of materials, the series has been divided into two groups: 1943-1987 and 1966-1968. Within each group, the index cards have been loosely organized alphabetically by subject.
  Index cards in the Unfiled series contain a subject term, a brief description of a topic, and a date. Materials from 1943 to 1987 only contain subject terms beginning with the letters A through W while materials from 1966 to 1968 contain subject terms beginning with the letters A through Z.
  - 1943-1987 (Offsite-box 123)
  - 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 123)